<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="T23c45574-4737-4537-8742-a865104c9310" xml:lang="en" class="- topic/topic " audience="dataClass"><title>properties Item</title><shortdesc>Part of the spatial hierarchy that describes a physical building or structure. Properties have a strict relationship with both Sites and Floors: a Property can be within one and only one Site, and wholly contains zero or more Floors. Properties may be contiguous with adjacent properties (whether or not they belong to the same Site) or discrete (separated by  land or other features). For contiguous/connected buildings, identification of where Property boundaries lie can be determined by considering the following: (i) if the users of the building have a specific name for it - for example &apos;North Tower&apos;, then it should be considered a separate Property even if it is physically connected to another Property at lower levels (and the low-level connecting structures are likely to be considered their own, separate Property); (ii) a Property is a physical description of space that is composed of a number of floors that - for the most part - are arranged one on top of the other (i.e. each floor is completely or largely overlapping the floor below). Properties also usually allow containment to be determined - someone or something should be either &apos;in&apos; or &apos;out&apos; of the Property. This can be particularly helpful when understanding Properties that represent outside structures like surface parking, play areas or sports fields.</shortdesc><body><table frame="all"><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="c1"/><colspec colname="c2"/><thead><row><entry namest="c1" nameend="c2">properties Item</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry><xref keyref='Eproperty-id'>property_id</xref> : integer</entry><entry>0..1</entry></row><row><entry><xref keyref='Eproperty-name'>property_name</xref> : string</entry><entry>0..1</entry></row><row><entry><xref keyref='Esite-id'>site_id</xref> : integer</entry><entry>0..1</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table><table frame="all"><tgroup cols="5"><colspec colname="c1"/><colspec colname="c2"/><colspec colname="c3"/><colspec colname="c4"/><colspec colname="c5"/><thead><row><entry>Source multiplicity</entry><entry>Source class</entry><entry>Association</entry><entry>Target class</entry><entry>Target multiplicity</entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry>0</entry><entry>investigation Module Data Model</entry><entry>properties</entry><entry>properties Item</entry><entry>far multiplicity is not defined</entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table><fig><title>Class Diagram</title><svg-container><svgref keyref="svg-properties-item"/></svg-container></fig></body></topic>